How are you doing?
You know, it's very bittersweet, but you
know, I I was just saying over there,
it's just how nice it is to have the
pleasure of watching one player
player's entire career, long career in
one place and do it so well and
and everything he was. I I you know, a
lot of people don't get a lot of
organizations don't get that, don't get
the privilege of having that, and we're
just
been privileged to watch him play all
these years and be part of the
organization.
He meant so much because over the course
of his career
he was here in some not so great times
and then
persevered through it to see the back
end of it in much better times. So,
you know, there are many times that he'd
be in that locker room and I will never
forget this one moment. We had a little
losing streak going on in the last
couple years,
and he walked in there
and passionately as somebody could say
it, he's like, "You do not want to go
back to what that dark place.
You do not want to go back to that dark
place." And not everybody knew what he
meant, but he lived it and was able to
communicate that to other people.
Sure, what comes to your mind when you
think of Lavonte David? Any particular
moment or any particular play?
I I just what I see in my head is really
two things. If ball on the ground, it's
probably Lavonte David who caused that
fumble. And it's doesn't matter where he
was on the field, you saw that tackle
boom down.
All over the place all the time, 100%
effort,
smile on his face, and just a quality,
quality person.
All right.
Thanks.